### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/iamaniket (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Python

Java

Machine Learning

#### Certifications

Ethical hacking

Java

Industrial visit

Android

Development

# **Aniket Yadav**

|| Python | Machine Learning ||

Ghaziabad, Uttar Pradesh, India

## Summary

Experienced Network Analyst with a demonstrated history of working in the Information Technology & Services industry. Skilled in Python (Programming Language), Microsoft Word, Java, HTML, and Adobe Photoshop. Strong information technology professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Computer Science from Ideal Institute Of Technology.

## Experience

Capgemini

Analyst

February 2020 - Present (2 months)

Hinjewadi

**HCL** Technologies

Analyst

March 2019 - November 2019 (9 months)

Noida Area, India

Hewlett Packard Enterprise Artificial intelligence internship June 2018 - July 2018 (2 months)

the wander bottles Sales And Marketing Intern December 2016 - March 2017 (4 months)

### Education

Ideal Institute Of Technology
Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (2015 - 2019)

Bhai Parmanand vidya mandir school

Intermediate, Computer Science · (2013 - 2015)

St. Thomas School

High school · (2007 - 2013)